http://www.mdsbooks.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Mark Senior, trading as MDS Book Sales collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://www.mdsbooks.co.uk/ website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by MDS Book Sales.
Personal identification information
Personal information is only collected automatically in order for fulfilment of an order to occur.  Data is only shared with our carriers (who are all compliant with GDPR).
Those wishing to receive the newsletter need to opt in.  If you no longer wish to receive the newsletter at any point then please use the ‘Unsubscribe’ option.
Any details stored (by agreement) are done so in a secure location under appropriate supervisions
No personal information is passed to Third Parties.
Our records are updated periodically to ensure that they remain as accurate as possible.
Should there be any queries please contact mark@mdsbooks.co.uk
Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, however, be aware that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilised and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. Users’ web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
MDS Book Sales may use Uasers (agreed) personal information for the following purposes:
v  To improve customer service - Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
v  To personalise user experience - We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
v  To process payments - We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
v  To send periodic emails - We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their enquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
MDS Book Sales has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
